#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/peggylaiyk (LinkedIn) peggylai.webflow.io (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Usability Testing
User Experience Design (UED)
UX Research

# Peggy Lai

**UI/UX** Designer

North York, Ontario, Canada

## Summary

Hi, I'm Peggy Lai, a super passionate and creative UI/UX designer with 3 years of experience. I absolutely love design and believe it has the power to make a real impact. I'm all about creating intuitive and visually stunning interfaces that really wow users. Let's collaborate and create something awesome together!

## Experience

New World Development Company Limited UI/UX Designer
July 2021 - February 2023 (1 year 8 months)
Hong Kong SAR

- Enhanced enrollment in K Dollar program by 30% through the implementation of a simplified onboarding process for the NWD's subsidiaries app.
- Developed a tablet-based restroom feedback system for 600+ users within the facility, involving the creation of a user journey map, flowchart, system diagram, and comprehensive research.
- Utilized Figma to create the interface for Citi Bank point conversion within the K11 mall app, employing a user-centered approach for wireframing and prototyping.
- Oversaw the creation of advanced data visualizations for an administrative portal utilized by 20+ employees, facilitating the monitoring of a blockchain dataset 1000+ records.
- Improved the coherence of the design system library, ensuring consistency across 100+ components and 300+ icons.

Tutor Circle
UI/UX Designer
January 2021 - June 2021 (6 months)

#### Hong Kong SAR

- Revamped an illustrative storytelling landing page that resulted in a 40% increase in conversion rate, achieved through the application of A/B Testing and Google Analytics to assess conversion performance.
- Conducted questionnaire survey with 50+ tutors through phone interviews; analysed the the merits and pain points of the Tutor Pass through a SWOT analysis approach.
- Enhanced the matching rate of tutors holding the Tutor Pass by 60%, ensuring that they were connected with students within 2 weeks.
- Lead the subscription of the Tutor Pass service by 1000+ tutors, enhancing their potential for student matching.

Tech Vision System Ltd.
Graphic Designer Internship
July 2019 - December 2019 (6 months)
Hong Kong SAR

- Enhanced user exploration through the redesign of the website and site map using Adobe XD.
- Created a compelling marketing booklet featuring 14 project showcases, aimed at effectively reaching the target audience.

#### Education

City University of Hong Kong

Bachelor of Science - BS, Creative Media · (September 2018 - August 2020)

Community College of City University

Associate's degree, Creative and Interactive Media Production · (September 2016 - August 2018)